let's say you have many objects that are
假设您有许多对象，这些对象
the same and at a later point you want
相同的，在以后的某一点上，您希望
to adjust them then you could use
要调整它们，您可以使用
cloning let's create a custom
克隆让我们创建一个定制
bullet I select the rectangle tool and
项目符号我选择矩形工具，然后
drag a rectangle to get rounded Corners
拖动矩形以获得圆角
I drag the circle shape control widget
我拖动圆形形状控件小部件
down I want the rectangle to stay alive
向下，我想让长方形活下去
shape so I will not convert it to a path
形状，这样我就不会将其转换为路径
I press the space
我按下空格键
bar in my layers I will set the blend
在我的层中设置条我将设置混合
mode to multiply now I will clone the
模式以进行倍增现在我将克隆
rectangle
长方形
you clone an object by pressing alt d i
您可以通过按Alt d i来克隆对象
drag the Clone down for my bullet I need
把克隆人拖下来找我需要的子弹
a second rectangle so I will clone the
第二个矩形，因此我将克隆
original again I click on the rectangle
我又一次点击了这个矩形
again so I can rotate it I hold control
再一次，这样我就可以旋转它了，我控制着它
and rotate at
并在以下位置旋转
90° I turn on snapping and open the menu
90°我打开捕捉并打开菜单
I want the corners of the bounding boxes
我想要包围盒的边角
to snap I select both rectangles and
要捕捉，我选择两个矩形和
click on them again so I can rotate I
再次单击它们，以便我可以旋转
hold control and rotate 45°
按住控制键并旋转45度
I want to add a third rectangle and I
我想添加第三个矩形，然后我
want the two clones to mask it so I
希望这两个克隆人能掩盖它，这样我
right click on the rectangles and choose
右键单击矩形，然后选择
set clip group now I clone the original
现在设置剪辑组我克隆原始的
again I drag the Clone in place to mask
我再一次将克隆人拖到适当的位置以遮盖
I drag the Clone on the clip group now
我现在将克隆拖动到剪辑组中
let's say I want the rectangles to be
比方说，我希望这些矩形是
shorter to do this I drag the left side
为缩短此操作，我拖动左侧
of the original end because the
原来的结局，因为
rectangle is still Al live shape the
矩形仍然是活的形状
corners will stay round after scaling
角落在缩放后将保持不变
now I select the bullet and clone it we
现在我选择子弹并克隆它
see the Clone now is a single shape I
现在看到的克隆人是一个单一的形状
will create a layer for it and call it
将为其创建一个层并将其命名为
bullets I call the other layer parents I
子弹我称另一层为父层
drag the single- shaped bullet on the
将单一形状的项目符号拖到
bullet's layer I select the parent
项目符号的层我选择父级
objects and drag them on the paste board
对象并将它们拖到粘贴板上
now I will hide them I don't have to
现在我会把它们藏起来，我不需要
clone the newest object anymore I can
我可以再克隆最新的物体
just duplicate it I will activate
只需复制它，我将激活它
alignment and select same distances I
对齐并选择相同的距离
can now duplicate instances of the
现在可以复制
Bullet by pressing the space bar
按空格键的项目符号
now let's say I want the bullets to be
现在假设我希望子弹是
smaller I show
我展示的更小
parents when I make the parent bullets
当我制作父母子弹时，父母
smaller the children will follow I hold
我认为，小孩子们会跟着
shift plus control while scaling and to
在缩放时转移加控制和到
change the color of the bullets I select
更改我选择的项目符号的颜色
the original rectangle in fill and
填充原始矩形，
stroke I adjust the color and I make the
笔画我调整颜色并制作
arms of the bullets a bit shorter
子弹的手臂短一点